{
    "id": "4470390e8b73400db31b8ef168302dc3",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I may be blunt …………………… at least I am honest.",
            "description": "We use but to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "672a9e9fc2394b60ae307032467f4b2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is beautiful …………………. she squints a little.",
            "description": "Although is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "however",
                "even if"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac2a4e4e909543008fe5fdd51818d4c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was …………………….. tired that he could barely stand.",
            "description": "The conjunction so...that... shows cause and effect. ",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a9fd4002b1d4b38bcfa5295c47d1fe1"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will get the award ……………………… you deserve it.",
            "description": "We use if to express a condition. ",
            "answers": [
                "whether",
                "if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4c8fa3d5f9564a4cb44180f4c8d95455"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will not get the job ………………….. you succeed in the interview.",
            "description": "Unless is similar to if not. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d1c9f6ede17d4487abcbd75d049e30f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… she is of noble birth, she is not rich.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Since"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc0ab560cd244493a757fac9a9b94567"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. there is life, there is hope.",
            "description": "All of these can be used here with slightly different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "As",
                "Since",
                "While",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "2863aa1486874677b4b49e727ad37b20"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… you have apologized, I will not sack you.",
            "description": "All of these words indicate the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "As",
                "Because",
                "All of these"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "8332653d07e74beabeb238f1c5f49736"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………….. he was the most deserving candidate, they appointed him.",
            "description": "Since can indicate the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Since",
                "Though",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "707e7a4acea544188733bda5a3cc02dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Generally speaking, the houses in ……………………… the Burmese live are made of bamboo.",
            "description": "In which can mean where. ",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "58777cdb0e3141e2bdaf213194870be4"
        },
        {
            "question": "He kept quiet …………………….. the argument might stop.",
            "description": "That can indicate the purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "hence",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7eb2f9c0787e4ad689891cab9ef22d1b"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… he was sick, he stayed at home.",
            "description": "As indicates the reason. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "In case",
                "As"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0aae08260f794a6baa2450aed3b22b30"
        }
    ]
}